So now you know some ways to ask about what's going to happen in the future.
所以现在你知道了一些询问未来会发生什么的方法。
We need to actually know how to talk about the future but to do that we have to put them.
我们实际上需要知道如何谈论未来，但要做到这一点，我们必须把它们放进去。
I think the different phrases into levels of certainty and the reason I think it makes sense to break
我认为将不同的短语划分为确定性级别以及我认为打破的原因是有意义的
up the phrases into levels of certainty is because when we describe what may or will happen in the future
将短语提高到确定性水平是因为当我们描述未来可能或将要发生的事情时
we use phrases that show that either it must be in the future or we want it to be in the future or we
我们使用的短语表明它必须在未来，或者我们希望它在未来，或者我们
think it will happen in the future but we're not sure.
认为它会在未来发生，但我们不确定。
Or we just have no idea.
或者我们只是不知道。
OK so let's look at some of these.
好的，让我们来看看其中的一些。
The first one is the most certain we use.
第一个是我们使用的最确定的。
I'm going to and I will to be very clear about the future.
我要去，而且我将非常清楚未来。
We say for example I'm going to buy my bus ticket tomorrow.
例如，我们说我明天要买巴士票。
I'm going to buy my plane ticket tomorrow.
我明天要去买我的机票。
Now notice that I'm not saying I'm going to the supermarket.
现在请注意，我并不是说我要去超市。
That's a different I'M GOING TO THAT I'M GOING TO THE SUPERMARKET means you're actually driving or walking.
这是一个不同的我要去超市，这意味着你实际上是在开车或走路。
OK.
好的。
That's a different one.
那是另一回事。
That's a different meaning.
那是不同的意思。
This going to means will it's the same thing.
这意味着它将是同一件事。
And then we say the action after going to we say I'm going to go I'm going to do so we use the simple
然后我们说去之后的动作我们说我要去我要去所以我们使用简单的
verb after it.
后面的动词。
I'm going to buy I'm going to eat I'm going to meet my friend tomorrow at 3:00 p.m. I'm going to meet
我要去买 我要去吃饭 我要去见我的朋友明天下午 3:00我要去见
my friend tomorrow at 3:00 p.m. I'm going to do my homework until about 10:00 we're very sure about
我的朋友明天下午 3:00我会做作业直到大约 10:00 我们非常确定
these things it's certain we often connect times to it at 3:00 at 5:00 p.m. at 10 p.m. If we say I will
可以肯定的是，我们经常在下午 3:00 和下午 5:00 将时间与它联系起来。晚上 10 点如果我们说我会
it's the same thing I will be home by 10:00 I will be home by 10:00 I will buy you an iPad for Christmas
是一样的 我会在 10:00 之前到家 我会在 10:00 之前到家 我会在圣诞节给你买一台 iPad
although you shouldn't tell people what you're going to get them for Christmas but it should be something
虽然你不应该告诉人们圣诞节你要给他们买什么，但它应该是一些东西
you are certain about then when we have a little less certainty we just add probably to Will.
当我们不太确定时，您可以确定，我们可能只是将其添加到 Will 中。
So by putting this here that means it's a little less clear I will probably get you a good birthday
所以把这个放在这里意味着不太清楚我可能会给你一个美好的生日
gift or I will probably go downtown tomorrow I'm not sure something might happen to stop me from doing
礼物，否则我明天可能会去市中心 我不确定会发生什么事情阻止我做
that.
那。
OK.
好的。
I plan to again means that we really think that we will but maybe something will happen.
我计划再次意味着我们真的认为我们会，但也许会发生一些事情。
So this one is pretty certain if we plan to do something but there are often when we have plans things
因此，如果我们计划做某事，这是非常确定的，但通常当我们有计划时
that happen which are unexpected and what can we do about those things.
发生的事情是出乎意料的，我们可以对这些事情做些什么。
Right.
正确的。
So I plan to take a vacation next summer to Japan next summer is maybe pretty far from now.
所以我打算明年夏天去日本度假，明年夏天可能离现在还很远。
It's a pretty long way off.
这是一个相当长的路要走。
So you plan to but something could happen right.
因此，您计划这样做，但某些事情可能会正确发生。
It could even be something that happens today for example I plan to go shopping later this afternoon.
它甚至可能是今天发生的事情，例如我计划今天下午晚些时候去购物。
I plan to go shopping later this afternoon but we might say that when someone else has mentioned that
我计划今天下午晚些时候去购物，但我们可能会说，当其他人提到时
they would like to do something with us that's different than that they might say I had planned to go
他们想和我们做一些不同于他们可能说我计划去的事情
shopping which means maybe I'm about to change my plan.
购物，这意味着我可能要改变我的计划了。
OK.
好的。
We can also use I'm planning to.
我们也可以使用 I'm planning to。
That's pretty common too.
这也很常见。
I'm planning to and often planning is for longer term things not so much near-term.
我正在计划并且经常计划的是长期的事情而不是短期的事情。
You can but it's often for long term.
你可以，但通常是长期的。
OK now we go down to the next level.
好的，现在我们进入下一个级别。
Less certain.
不太确定。
I'd like to.
我想。
This means that we just want it.
这意味着我们只是想要它。
It really has no connection to how sure we are about whether or not it will happen.
它真的与我们对它是否会发生的确定程度无关。
I'd like to go to Seattle next week.
我想下周去西雅图。
I'd like to.
我想。
I'd like to go on vacation next year to Europe.
我想明年去欧洲度假。
We have no idea it might happen.
我们不知道它可能会发生。
It might not.
可能不会。
I might I might I might quit my job next year.
我可能我可能会在明年辞掉我的工作。
Now that means we're just thinking about it.
现在这意味着我们只是在考虑它。
I might quit my job next year.
明年我可能会辞职。
Will it happen.
会不会发生。
There's a chance because if I'm thinking about it that means that could lead to my action my quitting
有机会，因为如果我正在考虑这意味着这可能会导致我采取行动，我会退出
the job.
工作。
Right.
正确的。
So OK it could happen.
好吧，它可能会发生。
I might I might I might buy a house I might buy a house this year I might say it's possible it's hard
我可能 我可能 我可能买房子 我可能今年买房子 我可能会说这可能很难
to put a percentage on that though I'm thinking about thinking about this is very similar to I might
尽管我正在考虑考虑这与我可能非常相似
very similar almost exactly the same I'm thinking about the only difference here is that we will use
非常相似 几乎完全一样 我在想这里唯一的区别是我们将使用
I and G I'm thinking about buying a house I'm thinking about asking my boss if I can come into work
我和G 我在考虑买房 我在想问问老板我能不能上班
late on Tuesdays because of my party's class I'm thinking about that will I do it.
周二晚了，因为我聚会的课，我在想我会不会这样做。
Maybe maybe not.
也许也许不是。
Okay same as I might.
好吧，和我可能的一样。
But the grammar is a little different now if we say.
但是如果我们说，现在的语法有点不同。
I hope we just have no idea the result could be this or this.
我希望我们只是不知道结果可能是这个或这个。
It could be a it could be B just have no clue so you could just say I hope I can get a good job.
可能是 A 可能是 B 只是不知道所以你可以说我希望我能找到一份好工作。
I hope I can get a good job.
我希望我能找到一份好工作。
I hope I can go on vacation but you just have no clue.
我希望我可以去度假，但你不知道。
It's totally uncertain the future is a mystery to you.
完全不确定未来对你来说是个谜。
Oh I hope it doesn't rain tomorrow.
哦，我希望明天不会下雨。
I hope it doesn't rain tomorrow.
我希望明天不会下雨。
If you hope it doesn't rain tomorrow you really don't know and you definitely don't have any control
如果你希望明天不下雨你真的不知道你肯定没有任何控制
over that.
在那之上。
OK so we go this way when we decrease our certainty vs this one this one and this one are often used
好的，所以当我们降低确定性时，我们就走这条路
to express what we would like.
来表达我们想要的。
We're thinking about it.
我们正在考虑。
Our desire.
我们的愿望。
These two are a little less certain than the first two but are more like the first two because we do
这两个比前两个不确定，但更像前两个，因为我们这样做
have the intention to do that or at least we think it's likely.
有这样做的意图，或者至少我们认为这是可能的。
These are absolutely clear and this one is just yes no could be either one.
这些是绝对清楚的，这个是肯定的，不可以是任何一个。
We could say a 50 50 chance a 50 50 chance.
我们可以说 50 50 机会 50 50 机会。
So these are the common phrases we use to discuss the future.
所以这些是我们用来讨论未来的常用短语。
There are more but these are probably the most common and the most useful phrases that we can use when
还有更多，但这些可能是我们可以使用的最常见和最有用的短语
we want to explain our feelings our intentions about the future.
我们想解释我们的感受我们对未来的意图。